hello let me introduce our startup idea that we have implemented during the hackathon so first
let's introduce ourselves we are either graduates or students of worse of university of technology we
come from diverse backgrounds and data science machine learning web development and business and we are
all members of golem association
the problem we have noticed during our studying and doing a contact of academia and with
a research offense is that research is really really hard and writing in the tech is
also really hard so how about we make it a whole lot easier our solution is
to implement a get up copilot but for low-tech documents so what should this solution do
we discuss between ourselves and with our research or friends and we believe that we pinpointed
the three most important features that this solution should have the first one is real-time text
outer completion for both lotic and natural language the second feature is suggestions for citations and
assistance in creating bibliography and the third one is conducting a comprehensive review of the paper
to give constructive feedback to the user